Adeyinka Adewojo

Management Information Systems Graduate Student

Graduate Student of Management Information Systems with 6 years of experience in Operations, Data Analysis, Reporting and Product Support. Seeking to apply my excellent leadership, client engagement, problem solving, analytical and communication skills to fulfill a data-oriented company's business requirements.

Work History

2018-09 -Current

General Office Assistant

UI Health Cancer Center, Chicago, IL

- Kept physical files and digitized records organized for easy updating and retrieval by authorized team members.
- Entered study data using Oncore, following procedures to keep information private.
- Interacted with medical personnel's professionally by phone, email or in-person to provide and retrieve information for clinical trials.
- Supported regulatory coordinators on special assignments, including study startup documentation and audit projects, through creation of study materials and document cleanups.

2013-10 -2018-07

Operations Manager

Huawei Technologies, Victoria Island, Lagos

- Initiated, monitored and completed payment reconciliation and settlement for all 3rd party media content providers.
- Functioned as the key interface for 3rd party media content providers to maximize service efficiency and revenue generation.
- Oversaw the vetting process for all 3rd party media content to ascertain conformance with telecoms regulatory provisions, and subsisting copyright guidelines.
- Coordinated the Value Chain team of 4 employees and ensured over 90% of assigned tasks were completed.

Personal Info

Address

3452 South Oakley Avenue Chicago, IL, 60608

Phone

(773) 744-0727

E-mail

adeywojo@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/adeyinka-adewojo/

Skills

MS Excel



Data Analysis



Business Analysis



Business Reporting



SQL



Python



 Implemented a strategy to achieve an increase in monthly revenue of the Mobile Newspaper Service by 33%.

- Optimized the content providers payment processing duration reducing it by 42%.
- Developed detailed process documents and guides used for in-house and partner training.
- Prepared high-level daily, weekly, quarterly and yearly reports which were used by the management team for key decision making.

2011-08 - Product Support Engineer

XMN Technologies, Ikoyi, Lagos

- Recommended changes and improvements in products according to customer feedback.
- Reviewed all customer inquiries to understand project scope while managing internal disciplines to compliantly respond.
- Provided technical troubleshooting and problem solving for clients with installed system issues.
- Worked with the software developers to resolve technical problems, improve operations and provide exceptional customer service.
- Assisted in the data migration during a software swap for a client.
- Prepared procedural documentation for resolving issues.

Education

2013-04

2018-08 - Master of Science: Management Information Systems

Current University of Illinois At Chicago - Chicago, IL

2007-10 - Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

2011-04 Bowen University - Osun State, Nigeria

Certifications

2019-09 IBM Data Science

Tableau

